Guide to the Skagit County Oral History Project records 1962-1979
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Archie Grimbley (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, October 7, 1977; RIII-90 (Reel 2)
  Subjects: Tugboating on the Skagit River, Captain Elwell, Childhood on a stump farm in Burlington
- T. B. Morrison (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 10, 1977; RIII-91 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript(34 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Morrison Mill, Fidalgo Lumber and Box Company
- Conrad Shoemaker (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 10, 1977; RIII-92 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (18 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Saw filing, Bucking, Coming west from Nebraska
- Cora Hassan (Year of Birth: 1890) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 10, 1977; RIII-93 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (12 pages), Reel-to-reel (45 min)
  Subjects: Early Clear Lake area, Childhood years at Clear Lake, Related to the Kimbles (Mt. Vernon founders)
- Anna L. Noteboom (Year of Birth: 1887) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 11, 1977; RIII-94 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (25 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Coming west, Early Skagit Valley History, Early childhood.
- Milo Coffelt (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 12, 1977; RIII-95 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (14 pages), Cassette (1 hour 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Detailed description of working on early mail boats that ran to the San Juan Islands, Anacortes Mariners Pageant, Chinese
- Tinnia Burns Young (Year of Birth: 1884) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Pearl White, October 10, 1977; February 2, 1978; RIII-96, T1-2 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (80 pages), Cassette (3 hours 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Homesteading on the Skagit River, First set nets on the river, Joe Young, French Canadian, Shingle bolter
  Notes: One tape and two transcripts, dates don't match
- Margaret A. Lee (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 14, 1977, November 18, 1977; RIII-97, T1-2 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (55 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours 15 min)
  Subjects: Fishing the North Fork of the Lower Skagit River
  Notes: Two tapes and two transcripts, dates don't match
- Orval A. Fox (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 14, 1977; RIII-98 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (39 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Barber history (52 years), Singing for the dances in the 1920s, Experience with the Tarheels, Early Mt. Vernon, Logging camp adventures
- Karl Lindall (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 13, 1977; RIII-99 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (32 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Rockport, Homesteading, Logging, Heavy machinery on the dam, Moonshining, Work ethics and unionization, Donkeys and steam engines
- Ruth Brown (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 14, 1977; RIII-100 (Reel 2)
  Format: Transcript (19 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Bay View area, Some information on Alaska
- Anna and Charles Dibble (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Pearl White, October 14, 1977; RIII-101 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (38 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Homesteading, Five years on the Sauk River
- Claude E. Speer (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 28, 1977; RIII-102 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Columbia School, Rum running, Hobo camp, Little Chicago, Squealer Mathison, Depression, Food Riot, 1916 Flu epidemic, Codfish schooner Fanny Dutard
- Hans C. Jensen (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 19, 1977; RIII-103 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (16 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Diking, Nursery work, Early Fir Island
- Norman Hamburg (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 19, 1977; RIII-104, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (66 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Settling in LaConner, Sterling, Mt. Vernon, Early bicycles, Ford machine shop, 42 gears, Skagit snag boats, Steam River, Snags, Accidents
  Notes: One tape and two transcripts
- Markus Johansen (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 20 [1977]; RIII-105 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (33 pages), Cassette 1 hour 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Anacortes glass factory, Anacortes Water, Light, and Power Company engineer, Early schooling, Saw mills
- Mrs. Hurst Riggs (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 20, 1977; RIII-106 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (21 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Homesteading, O'Brien family, Marblemoount, Post mistress for twenty years
- Martin Sampson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Hazel Hartman, August 1, 1961; RIII-107 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Indian history, language, and songs
- Rangnar [Rangar] Peterson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, October 26, 1977; RIII-108 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (20 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Equality Colony, Farming, Blanchard area
- Marjorie R. Voth (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, October 26, 1977; RIII-109 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (43 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Skagit Indians, Pioneer Jackman, Tribal culture and history, Shaker church, Indian burial, Herbal cures, Marriage of Marjorie Voth's grandmother
- J. Lee Lindemood (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, November 1, 1977; RIII-110, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (57 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early diking, Floods, Farming, Circuses, Working for the visiting shows in Mt. Vernon
- Leonard R. Everett (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, November 2, 1977; RIII-111 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: History of the Cement Company in Concrete, 'Pegleg' Everett
- Frances Rivord (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 7, 1977; RIII-112 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (23 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Coming west from North Carolina, Early Sedro-Woolley, Early widowhood, Nine children
- Mary Luvera (Mrs. Paul Luvera) (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 9, 1977; RIII-113 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (35 pages), Cassette (45 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Discussion of John Barbarovich, early settler, Farming on Sinclair Island
- Guy Powell (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, November 9, 1977, February 24, 1978; RIII-114, T1a,b,c-2a,b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (182 pages), Cassette (6 hours 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Concrete, Packers, Indians, Shakers, Gambling, Bars, Sporting Girls, Cock fights, Politics, Hunting, Shaker church, Indian dugouts, Moonshining, The concrete plant, Bootleging
  Notes: four tapes and five transcripts
- P. H. Dunlap (Bud) (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 10, 1977; RIII-115 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Early farming, Threshing, Diking, Steamboats, LaConner area
- Alice Jensen (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 11, 1977; RIII-116 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: West from Tennessee, Pleasant Ridge School, Early LaConner, Carpentry, Dressmaking
- Bessie Charawell Jarboe Koudal (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Jean Sickler, June 12, 1979; RIII-117 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Goat Island, Fort Whitman, Transportaiton to and from school and church by boat, Early LaConner, WWI, WWII
- Charles E. Benedict (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 15, 1977; RIII-118, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (61 pages), Cassette (2 hours 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Oxen and horse logging, Donkeys in logging, Saw filing, Social security, Labor unions, Organization of the IWW
  Notes: two tapes and two transcripts
- Phil M. Iverson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Mike Rust, November 15, 1977; RIII-119 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (45 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Flood of 1932, Diking commissioner, Early farming, Clearing land on Fir Island, Norwegian community
- Nellie B. Tiscornia (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, November 16, 1977; RIII-120 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (26 pages), Cassette, Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Equality Colony, Edison school, Basketball and track teams, Logging cook, Flunkey
- Stella M. Long (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 17, 1977; RIII-121 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Food, Healing, Living, Grandmother's role as a teacher, Boarding at the Tulalip Indian School, Face and body painting, Seeking the Holy Spirit
- Col. G. E. Reed (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 17, 1977; RIII-122 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (6 pages), Cassette (30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Logging, Pharmacy
- Ed Stafford (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Jim Harris, November 18, 1977; RIII-123 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (13 pages), Cassette (2 hours 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Coming west from North Carolina to Rockport, Welcomed by Skagit Bill, Sporting houses of Concrete
- Carl R. Olin (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 21, 1977; RIII-124 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (16 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Cedardale, Loading hay into the barn, IWW and their effects on logging
- Lloyd R. King (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 29, 1977; RIII-125 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (43 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours 30 min)
  Subjects: Arrival in Concrete, Working on the Baker River and Shuksan Railroad for the Concrete plant, working in the woods and for the Forest Service, Mining, Prospecting, Forest fires, Trail work
- Marion O. Berentson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 29, 1977; RIII-126, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (71 pages), Cassette (2 hours 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Mill accidents, Japanese snubbers, Lumber piler, Early Edison, Norwegian community, Riding rails with an IWW card, Politics in his and his children's lives (Duane)
- Edwin A. Kittila (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, November 29, 1977; RIII-127, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (70 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: History of the Finnish settlement, Lake McMurray area, Neighbors, Scandalous school teachers, Farming, Logging, Saunas
  Notes: one tape and two transcripts
- John Hedlund and Carl Anderson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 30, 1977; RIII-128 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (35 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Immigration from Sweden, Early farming on the Skagit Valley Flats, Depression years, Farm machinery and technology
  Notes: Editor's note: the first part of interview RIII-129 is on side 2 of this tape (Carl Anderson)
- Carl A. Anderson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 30, 1977; RIII-129 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Harmony School, Childhood spent in Skagit County, Early dairy farming, Hop houses, Farm technology, Migrant Indians
  Notes: Editor's note: the first part of interview RIII-129 is on side 2 of this tape (Hedlund/Anderson)
- Orvia F. Parker (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, November 30, 1977; RIII-130, a, b (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (66 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours 30 min)
  Subjects: Cod fishing, the Wawona schooner of the Robinson Fish Company of Anacortes in the 1930s, Details of the ship, Dory, How to fish, Wildlife, Crew, Captain
  Notes: Two tapes and transcripts
- Roland L. Lewis (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, December 1, 1977, January 20, 1977; RIII-131, T1 a, b -2 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (62 pages), Cassette (3 hours 20 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Equality Colony, Julia Haroldson, Early Edison, Samish Island Murder, Father was the cook in a logging camp on Samish Island
  Notes: two tapes and three transcripts
- Kathleen Sharpe (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, December 7, 1977; RIII-132 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (24 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Origins of the Ervine and Sharpe families, Teaching at the Rosario school, Sharpe settlement on Fidalgo Island
- Vashti Hooper (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, December 13, 1977; RIII-133 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Early Rockport area, Farming, Schools
- Mary O'Loughlin (and Lillian) (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, December 15, 1977; RIII-134 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (7 pages), Reel-to-reel (45 min)
  Subjects: Early LaConner, Farming, School teaching, Cokedale school, Bellingham Normal
- Alice Nelson Deierlein (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, December 16, 1977; RIII-135 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (29 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Logging, Father ran the mill, Childhood years in Montbourne-Big Lake area
- John Uitto (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, December 20, 1977; RIII-136 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (30 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: IWW, Finnish settlement, Laplanders, Sumas socialism
- Ethel E. Bjork (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, December 20, 1977; RIII-137 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (19 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Edison history (a great deal), Dances, Events, Pregnancy
- Carolyn Spencer and Grace Conner (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, December 29, 1977; RIII-138 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Oxen logging, Skid road, Dogfish oil
- Mamie Mumford (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, January 11, 1978; RIII-139 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (33 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Thornwood Logging Camp, Growing up in logging camps, Music in the camp, Cooking for the men, Death of high rigger husband
- Signe Ashland and Levina Johnson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, January 17, 1978; RIII-140 (Reel 3)
  Subjects: Fish traps, Fishing, Midwifery, Swedish immigrants, Women gillnetters, Crab fished to send daughter to college
- Jean Forrest (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, January 17, 1978; RIII-141 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (41 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Burden's hop farm on March's Point, Basket socials, Harry Rickaby, Minnie Burden
- Mary T. Luvera (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, January 18, 1978; RIII-142 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (19 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 45 min)
  Subjects: Preserving foods, Home remedies for burns and other ailments, Early fishing, Family life, Recipes, the Luvera grocery store
- Annie Brunzel (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, January 23, 1978; RIII-143 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (22 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Anacortes, Schools, Fourth of July celebrations
- Elmer Vogt (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, January 30, 1978; RIII-144 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (48 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Fish trapping for 18 years, Mail boat through the San Juans, Rum runners, boat building, Reef net boats, History of logging wheels at the Skagit County Historical Museum in LaConner
- Jalmer I. Moe (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 3, 1978; RIII-145 (Reel 3)
  Format: Transcript (47 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Logging, Railroad engineer for the English Logging Company, General explanation fo railroad terminology, Identified several pictures taken by D. Kinsey
- Herbert J. Woodfield (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 6, 1978; RIII-146 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (34 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Bayview, Logging in Bayview, The English Logging Company, Sporting houses of Anacortes and Sedro-Woolley, Boats
- Bert Jones (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, February 7, 1978; RIII-147, a, b (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Fish pirating, Bootlegging, Rum smuggling, Cannery work, Fishing, Mike Demopolis, Anna Curtis
  Notes: two tapes and transcripts
- William J. Beale (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 8, 1978; RIII-148 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (29 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Fishing at Neah Bay, Grandfather Beale was the first settler of Fidalgo Island 185?, 40 years at the Anacortes post office
- Bartol Lovric (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 9, 1978; RIII-149 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (8 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Mostly about Yugoslavia, Receiving naval architect training in Yugoslavia, Building family shipyard, Shipyard under communism, Discussion of boats recently built
  Notes: Tape is in Slavonian
- Harry Bjerstedt (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 8, 1978; RIII-150, a, b (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Swan Bjerstedt's (his father) homesteading on Oly Marsh, Diking, Draining, Horse logging, Farming the peat bog flats, Sporting houses of Sedro-Woolley
- Eva G. Feldt (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 10, 1978; RIII-151 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (16 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Early Whitney area, Childhood years at Whitney, Fourth of July celebration spent in Anacortes, Homesteading in Alberta
- Alma O'Connor and Ethel Thompson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, February 14, 1978; RIII-152 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (52 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Growing up at Van Horn, Working at the Depot's restaurant, Phone company, Nell Quackenbush, Floods of the Skagit River
- William (Bill) Mason (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 16, 1978; RIII-153 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Superintendent of the English Logging Company
- Prudence A. Hattie (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 16, 1978; RIII-154 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Equality Colony, Box socials, Homesteading in Alger
- Mary McLeod (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 17, 1978; RIII-155 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (20 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Childhood at Skiyou, Ran the dance hall and store at Marblemount, Bought and ran the old Pressentin Hotel
- Emil Yougquist [Youngquist] (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 21, 1978; RIII-156, a, b (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript 56 pages), Cassette (2 hours 20 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early farming, Homesteading, Dairy breeding, Diking, Draining
- Estelene Martin Pearson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 23, 1978; RIII-157 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (11 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Telephone operator in Burlington in 1916, Worked during WWI in a sawmill with other women
- Margaret Clair Young (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 23, 1978; RIII-158 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Munks family, RN training, Earlier settlers of the Similk area, Fourth of July celebrations in Anacortes
- J. H. Hulbert, Sr. (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 23, 1978; RIII-159 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (4 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Floods, Diking, Draining, Farming, Holsteins
- Reuben R. Boyd (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, February 23, 1978; RIII-160 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (52 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Logging, Lokey firing, Running donkey, Card rooms, Bootlegging
- Herbert S. Rolph (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, February 28, 1978; RIII-161 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Working as a lumber grader, the Anacortes Lumber and Box Company, the WPA, Wobblies, Beekeeping
- Mr. and Mrs. Bill Henry (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 2, 1978; RIII-162 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (28 pages), Reel-to-reel (2 hours)
  Subjects: Prohibition, Tennessee immigrants, Hound dogs
- Albert V. Ginnett (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, March 1, 1978; RIII-163, T1 a, b - 6 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (115 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Ginnett homestead on Fidalgo Island, the Western Union, Mining, Bootlegging, Anacortes booms and busts, Indians, Rosario beach, Canneries, Shipbuilding
  Notes: one tape and four folders containing transcripts, 2 copies of T 1 a, b
- George Erickson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 1, 1978; RIII-164 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Homesteading on the flats, Avon, Pleasant Ridge, Early farming, Diking, Draining, Horses, Milk route, Machinist in Everett, Witness to Verona and Wobbly massacres
- Edith Robinson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 8, 1978; RIII-165 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (30 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Subjects: Sid Chee, Chinese, Robinson's Salmon Cannery, Chinese cannery workers, Early Anacortes, Salina, Dances, the Rhododendron Festivals
- Esther Culver (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 10, 1978; RIII-166
  Format: Reel-to-reel (30 min)
  Subjects: Early information on the Edison and Allen areas
  Notes: Transcript missing
- May Elizabeth Tucker Ploeg (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 13, 1978; RIII-167 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (14 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Homesteading on the Nooksack, Cold cures, Family memories of aunts and uncles, May is a cousin of Darius and Tabitha Kinsey -- he worked for them in their darkroom in Seattle for a year.
- Ruth Shrewsbury Running (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 15, 1978; RIII-168 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (25 pages), Reel-to-reel (45 min)
  Subjects: Growing up in Sedro-Woolley, Early pioneers, Dances, History of the Shrewesbury family
- Mae Richmeyer (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 15, 1978; RIII-169 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (27 pages), Cassette (1 hour 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Birdsview, Darius Kinsey, Nell Quackenbush
- Albert H. Bingham (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 16, 1978; RIII-170 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Bingham Family Bank, Prohibition, Dollar Road
- Jess A. Knutzen (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 16, 1978; RIII-171 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (44 pages), Cassette (1 hour 45 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Family history, Dairy farming in Skagit Valley, Tule horse shoes, Threshing, Floods, Dikes, Drainage, Soil, Peat fires
- Blake R. Thompson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 16, 1978; RIII-172 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (12 pages), Reel-to-reel (30 min)
  Subjects: Brickyards, Drainage, Tile factory, Big Rock, 1916 to 1929
- Marie Jurkovich (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 17, 1978; RIII-173 (Reel 4)